http://www.omri.org/privacy-policy

Log In
E-mail*
Password*
Request new password
Have you forgotten your e-mail or password?New User or Logging in for the First time?
Request new password
Have you forgotten your e-mail or password?New User or Logging in for the First time?
Home » Community » Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting OMRI.org. This privacy policy tells you how we may use your personal information collected on this site. By using this site you are accepting the practices described on this page. OMRI is the sole owner of any and all information collected through the website at OMRI.org. OMRI uses Google Analytics to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on our site. This information helps us understand customer interests and improve our website. When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed. Our CommitmentOMRI does not collect any personal information about users, except that which is knowingly and specifically supplied. Information that is provided through the OMRI website may be stored on secure servers. OMRI and OMRI partners may use contact information that you provide to contact you in the interest of achieving OMRI’s mission, including sending surveys about your experience with OMRI. OMRI will not sell or transmit your information to other organizations. Personal and Credit Card InformationOMRI uses encryption and https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card and other information you send to us. Companies we work with to process credit card transactions also use high-grade encryption and security protocols. OMRI does not collect or store any credit card information.Non-Personal Information and “Cookies”Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by OMRI.org through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files that we (and most websites) pass to your computer’s hard disk through your web-browser. They are used to determine how many individuals use our site, how many people visit on a regular basis, which pages are most popular, and which pages are least popular. No personal information is stored in the cookies we collect; information collected this way simply allows us to monitor and improve our website. For more information about cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.External LinksOMRI.org provides some external links to other websites outside of our service. The operation of these web sites is beyond our control and OMRI does not endorse or accept responsibility for their content or privacy policies. Users should read the privacy statements of every website that collects personal or credit card information.
E-mail*
Password*
Request new password
Have you forgotten your e-mail or password?New User or Logging in for the First time?
OMRI for Consumers and Educators
OMRI for Farmers and Organic Professionals
OMRI for Certifiers
OMRI for Input Suppliers
Staff Menu
Application ToolsCrystal Ball
Application Kit Submissions
Online Initial Applications Submissions
Renewal Submissions
User UtilitiesSubscription Language Preference
UtilitiesTechnical Information Editor
Copyright ©2020 OMRI • PO Box 11558, Eugene, OR 97440-3758 USA • 541.343.7600 • fax 541.343.8971
Send us an email • Sitemap • Design and Web development by OMRI and Slub Design
Our site has detected that the browser you are using is not supported. In order to provide you the best experience with our site, you will need to use a supported browser.
Supported Browsers: Chrome, Firefox, and Edge.
